/* jshint esversion: 6 */
/* jshint -W033 */

// Questions - Lover

export const loverQuestions = [
    {
    "question": "Would've been right there, front row even if nobody came to your show",
    "answers": ["Cruel Summer", "Cornelia Street", "I Forgot that You Existed", "Paper Rings"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "He looks up, grinnin' like a devil",
    "answers": ["I Think He Knows", "The Archer", "Lover", "Cruel Summer"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "My heart's been borrowed and yours has been blue",
    "answers": ["Lover", "Soon You'll Get Better", "Afterglow", "False God"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Every conquest I had made would make me more of a boss to you",
    "answers": ["You Need to Calm Down", "The Man", "Lover", "Cruel Summer"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "All the king's horses, all the king's men couldn't put me together again",
    "answers": ["The Archer", "Paper Rings", "I Think He Knows", "Cornelia Street"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "He's so obsessed with me, and boy I understand",
    "answers": ["London Boy", "False God", "Lover", "I Think He Knows"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Now I've read all of the books beside your bed ",
    "answers": ["Afterglow", "Paper Rings", "I Forgot that You Existed", "London Boy"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "And baby, I get mystified by how this city screams your name",
    "answers": ["The Archer", "The Man", "London Boy", "Cornelia Street"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "He likes my American smile",
    "answers": ["London Boy", "Lover", "False God", "Afterglow"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "It's been years of hoping, and I keep saying it because",
    "answers": ["Paper Rings", "You Need to Calm Down", "Soon You'll Get Better", "Lover"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "I know heaven's a thing I go there when you touch me, honey",
    "answers": ["Lover", "False God", "Afterglow", "I Think He Knows"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "We all know now, we all got crowns",
    "answers": ["You Need to Calm Down", "I Forgot that You Existed", "Daylight", "The Man"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Fighting with a true love is boxing with no gloves",
    "answers": ["Paper Rings", "Lover", "I Think He Knows", "Afterglow"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Baby doll, when it comes to a lover I promise that you'll never find another",
    "answers": ["Lover", "ME!", "The Man", "The Archer"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Rice on the ground looks like snow",
    "answers": ["Afterglow", "Daylight", "It's Nice to Have a Friend", "False God"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Luck of the draw only draws the unlucky",
    "answers": ["Daylight", "Paper Rings", "Lover", "London Boy"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "We could leave the Christmas lights up 'til January",
    "answers": ["Cruel Summer", "I Think He Knows", "Afterglow", "Lover"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Who could ever leave me, darling? But who could stay?",
    "answers": ["The Archer", "You Need to Calm Down", "Afterglow", "ME!"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "He got that boyish look that I like in a man",
    "answers": ["The Man", "Paper Rings", "I Think He Knows", "Lover"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "I hate accidents except when we went from friends to this",
    "answers": ["Lover", "Paper Rings", "Cornelia Street", "False God"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "I blew things out of proportion, now you're blue",
    "answers": ["Afterglow", "The Man", "Cruel Summer", "London Boy"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Lost my gloves, you give me one",
    "answers": ["Lover", "Soon You'll Get Better", "Daylight", "It's Nice to Have a Friend"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "I'm so sick of running as fast as I can",
    "answers": ["You Need to Calm Down", "The Man", "The Archer", "Daylight"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "I've been sleepin' so long in a twenty-year dark night",
    "answers": ["Daylight", "ME!", "False God", "Afterglow"],
    "correct": 0
    }, 

    {
    "question": "Devils roll the dice, angels roll their eyes",
    "answers": ["London Boy", "The Man", "Cruel Summer", "Paper Rings"],
    "correct": 2
    },
];